<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Impromptu</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="slideone">seize "\n"the"\n"moment</string>
    <string name="skdetwo">broaden"\n"your"\n"horizons</string>
    <string name="slidethree">promote"\n"your"\n"events</string>

    <string name="slideonetext">choose from thousands of free events"\n"created by people like you</string>
    <string name="slidetwotext">do something new today, make"\n"friends in the process</string>
    <string name="slidethreetext">earn money and build a reputation by"\n"hosting events in your area</string>

    <string name="eventname">GYMBOX Lelcester Sq</string>
    <string name="eventDate">Tomorrow at 7PM</string>
    <string name="alreadyhaveaccount">business or charity?  <u>"<b>"register here"</b>"</u></string>
    <string name="donthaveaccount">Don\'t have an Account? <u>"<b>" SignUp"</b>"</u></string>

    <string name="perviewDescrition">Two friends from Central Saint Martins are attending this event having heard great things about last year’s show.  Includes a runway segment, a sample sale and the opportunity to interact with up and coming designers. Check out the link for further info.  Will probably grab some coffee and cake afterwards. Happy for a handful of likeminded others to join us….</string>
    <string name="perviewLocation">Kensington"\n"Town Hall Kensington W8 7NX"\n"London</string>
    <string name="text">Your opinion helps people make"\n"better decisions about which events to join."\n"Share your feedback with us!</string>
    <string name="thanksforcoming">thanks"\n"for"\n"coming!</string>

    <string name="businesstext1">Engage"\n"Your"\n"Community</string>
    <string name="businesstext2">First"\n"Month"\n"Free</string>
    <string name="bussDesc1">Whether you are an established business or an upstart looking to find its feet, our unique platform is a powerful tool for promoting your events to people nearby.</string>
    <string name="bussDesc2">Listing your event is simple, quick and you save a fortune in the process (£3.99 per event and 5% of any ticket cover). We are entirely free for registered charities!</string>

    <string name="alreadySignup">Already signed up?</string>
    <string name="ForgotPassword"><u>Forgot Password</u></string>
    <string name="login"><u>Login here</u></string>
    <string name="seemessages"><u>see messages for this event</u></string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">837238269949836</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb837238269949836</string>
    <string name="googleclientId">AIzaSyBv3FYZuLZJR8mOlONc6hMGqh-Taeo7-7g</string>
    <!--    <string name="googleclientId">AIzaSyBm_8oGbXAp_2Yoa0YI8ZAQWg16h9G-bvo</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="googleclientId">AIzaSyDKpkPtlJLZC0KR-p-cvb4QXG_5JtXFL40</string>-->
    <string name="userProfileQuestion">+ Answer up to three of these questions "\n" (Showcase your personality in the process)</string>
    <string name="userProfileStatus">Write a bit about yourself to share with other users</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="pref_key_transition_time"><![CDATA[<string name=\"pref_key_transition_time\" translatable=\"false\">pref_key_transition_time</string>]]></string>
    <string name="dialog_seekbar_transition_time"><![CDATA[<string name=\"dialog_seekbar_transition_time\">Item transition time in millis</string>]]></string>
    <string name="server_client_id">905451169371-f5bfnn34du4j1p41o3if6m6mjd4gsvlk.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">firebase_default_channel</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribed">Impromptu Notify</string>
    <string name="msg_subscribe_failed">Notify failed</string>
    <string name="feedback"><u>Leave Feedback</u></string>
    <string name="uniqueid"><b>Unique Event ID </b>(found in event listing)</string>
    <string name="contactuscomment">Any feedback? Any comments? "\n"Don’t be shy, give us a shout...</string>

    <string name="enter_location">Enter Location</string>
    <string name="auto_complete_text">Autocomplete textview with custom adapter.</string>
    <string name="error">Google Api key is missing.</string>
    <string name="privancypolicytext">By using Impromptu’s services, you consent to the collection and use of your data as described in this Privacy Policy. Please carefully read the following to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, disclose, protect and otherwise handle information about you.  "\n""\n"<b><font size="18">This policy details;</font></b> </string>
    <string name="agreement"><u>1.1: AGREEMENT</u></string>
    <string name="agreementtext">Impromptu facilitates you and other users meeting at ‘real world’ social events. These events are created, hosted and attended by Impromptu users. The terms “Impromptu,” “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to Impromptu Social Limited and our affiliates. We use the terms “you” and “your” to designate any person using our Platform and any organisation/person using the Platform on an organisation’s behalf. We utilise the term “Platform” with respect to any website, application or service offered by Impromptu Social Limited (including our content offered and electronic communications sent). We provide our Platform to you subject to these Terms of Service. Your use of the Platform signifies that you agree to this Agreement. If you are using the Platform for an organisation, you agree to this Agreement on behalf of said organization and indicate that you have authority to bind said organization to the terms contained herewith. If you do not or are unable to agree to this Agreement, do not use our Platform.</string>
    <string name="revision"><u>1.2: REVISIONS</u></string>
    <string name="revisiontext">This agreement is subject to modification. When modified, we will notify you by publishing the latest version and revising the date at the top of this page. In case of any material change to this Agreement, we will provide additional notice to you, either by email or displaying a clear notice on our Platform. By continuing to use the Platform after any changes come into effect, you agree to the revised Agreement</string>
    <string name="eligibilty"><u>2.1: ELIGIBILITY</u></string>
    <string name="eligibiltytext">Our Platform is available to anyone who is at least 18 years of age. You represent that you are at least 18. Additional eligibility requirements for a particular portion of our Platform may be set by any member who has the ability to moderate or manage that portion of our Platform. For example, the eligibility requirements for an Impromptu event may be set by the creator/host of the event.</string>
    <string name="suspension"><u>2.2: SUSPENSION</u></string>
    <string name="suspensiontext">We reserve the right to modify, suspend or terminate your account or access to the Platform if, in our sole discretion, we determine that you have (a) violated this Agreement (including any of the policies or guidelines that are part of this Agreement), (b) that it is in the best interest of the Impromptu community or (c) to protect our brand/Platform. We also may purge accounts of members who are inactive for an extended period of time."\n" "\n" Both event hosts and attendees have the opportunity to flag inappropriate behaviour and we reserve the right to act upon this information.</string>
    <string name="security"><u>2.3: SECURITY</u></string>
    <string name="securitytext">Upon registering, you provide us with some basic pieces of information, including an email address and a password. Ensure your email address and other account information is kept current and accurate. Furthermore, you agree to maintain the security and confidentiality of your password. If you fail to do this we may need to disable your account. You are solely responsible for anything that occurs from your failure to maintain this security and confidentiality (sharing your account details with others for example). If someone else is using your password, make sure to inform us immediately.</string>
    <string name="impromptufee"><u>3.1: IMPROMPTU FEES</u></string>
    <string name="impromptufeetext">Use of most of the features on our Platform is entirely free; this said we charge fees for some features. In the future we may implement a new fee, or modify an existing fee, for both certain current or future features of our Platform. If this happens will give advance notice to you, either by clear posts on our Platform or by sending you an email. You agree to pay those fees and any associated taxes for your continued use of the applicable service. Unless otherwise stated, all fees and all transactions are in the local currency of your location. Member subscriptions are non-transferable.</string>
    <string name="impromptuhostfee"><u>3.2: IMPROMPTU HOST FEES</u></string>
    <string name="impromptufeehosttext">Hosts may levy fees related to an event they have created. The decision to charge fees and the amount charged is at the discretion of these hosts. You should use common sense when deciding whether to make a payment to any host. We cannot ensure that hosts will use payments as they promise or as you would expect. You should clarify the refund policy of the host before making any payments to them.</string>
    <string name="paymenttext"><u>3.3: PAYMENTS</u></string>
    <string name="paymenttexts">Impromptu account holders are responsible for paying any event listing fees and ticket commission fees to Impromptu in a timely manner and through our approved payment methods. If we terminate, suspend, or remove your account in connection with violation of this Agreement, we are not obligated to refund any fees paid to Impromptu. You may only pay fees to Impromptu using a valid payment method acceptable to us, as specified on the Platform. You represent and warrant that you are authorised to use the payment method you designate via the Platform. You authorise us (and our designated third-party payment processors) to charge your designated payment method for the total amount of any fees you owe to Impromptu (including any applicable taxes and other charges). If the payment method cannot be verified, is invalid, or is otherwise unacceptable to us, your payment may be suspended or cancelled. We reserve the right to correct or to instruct our payment processors to correct any errors or mistakes, even if payment has already been requested or received.</string>
    <string name="renewal"><u>3.4: RENEWALS</u></string>
    <string name="renewaltext">Fees for certain aspects of our Platform may be billed on either a one-time or recurring basis. If billed on a recurring basis, the fees are payable in advance of the applicable period specified via the Platform with no refunds. We will automatically bill you for each renewal period until cancellation. By purchasing any feature or other aspect of our Platform for which we charge, you authorize us to keep your payment current by charging your credit card account (or any other means of payment used by you) the applicable fee. Whilst you may cancel your subscription at any time, you will not be issued a refund except at our sole discretion.</string>
    <string name="payment"><u>3.5: 3rd PARTY PAYMENTS</u></string>
    <string name="paymenttext1">Any host that uses the Platform to accept payments from other members must comply with the terms and conditions of the third party provider of the applicable payment service used to receive the payment. Impromptu does not provide those payment services, is not a party to your agreement with the applicable third-party provider and will not be liable or responsible for your use of those third-party payment services.</string>
    <string name="freetrails"><u>3.6: FREE TRIALS</u></string>
    <string name="freetrailstext">We may offer free trials various products and subscriptions on our Platform. After your free trial ends, you may be required to take a paid subscription, in which case we will automatically bill you for each renewal period until cancellation. You can cancel automatic subscription renewals at any time according to the terms and procedures described above.</string>
    <string name="conentprivacy">Your Content and Privacy</string>
    <string name="privacy"><u>4.1: PRIVACY</u></string>
    <string name="privancytext">Impromptu collects registration and other information about you through our Platform. Please refer to our Privacy Policy for details on how we collect, utilise and disclose this information. These policies do not govern use of information that you provide to third parties, such as other members of Impromptu’s Platform."\n""\n" Impromptu has no control over how other members may use information that you provide to them, so you should exercise common sense and good judgment when sharing information with others on our Platform.</string>
    <string name="yourcontent"><u>4.2: YOUR CONTENT</u></string>
    <string name="yourcontenttext">You are solely responsible for your Content. We use the word “Content” to refer to any information, material or other content posted to our Platform (or otherwise provided to us; examples include feedback, comments or suggestions shared with us). You agree that you and your Content shall not violate the rights of any third party (such as copyrights, trademarks, contract rights, privacy rights or publicity rights) or this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="contentlicence"><u>4.3: CONTENT LICENSE</u></string>
    <string name="contentlicencetext">We do not claim ownership of your Content. However, in order for us to operate, protect, better and promote Impromptu and our Platform (and to ensure we do not violate any rights you may have in your Content) you hereby grant Impromptu a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, global, royalty-free, sub-licensable, transferable right and license (including a waiver of any moral rights) to utilise, distribute, publish, publicly display, publicly perform, host, store, reproduce, modify and create derivative works of your Content and to commercialise and exploit the copyright, trademark, publicity and database rights you have in your Content.</string>
    <string name="platform">Your Use of Our Platform</string>
    <string name="platformtext">We require that that you follow our policies and guidelines when using our Platform. We have no responsibility for Content that anyone posts to our Platform.</string>
    <string name="guidelinetext">When you use our Platform, you also agree to comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations and to not violate or infringe the rights of any third party. If you do not comply, we may at our sole discretion, modify, suspend or terminate your account or access to the Platform,</string>
    <string name="contentother">Impromptu does not control the content of other members. When we become aware of inappropriate content on our Platform, we reserve the right to investigate and take appropriate action, but we do not have any obligation to monitor, nor do we take responsibility for the content of other members.</string>
    <string name="interactiontext">Impromptu is not a party to any offline arrangements made through our Platform. Impromptu does not conduct or require background checks on members and does not attempt to verify the truth or accuracy of statements made by members. Impromptu makes no representations or warranties concerning the conduct or content of any members or their interactions with you."\n""\n" Exercise common sense and good judgment when using our Platform and interacting with other members, both on our Platform and at Impromptu events. If you have a concern regarding other members, you can report it on platform or by emailing support@impromptu.com.</string>
    <string name="resaletext">Our Platform contains proprietary and confidential information and is protected by IP laws. Unless we expressly permit it through this Agreement, you agree not to modify, reproduce, sell or charge a fee, offer to sell or charge a fee, make/create derivative works based on or distribute any part of our Platform (including any data or Content of others).</string>
    <string name="tecnicaltext">You agree that you will not engage in any activity or post any information or material that interferes with, disrupts or that is designed to interfere with or disrupt the Platform (or any hardware used in connection with the Platform).</string>
    <string name="modificationtext">We work hard to continuously improve our Platform. This means that we may modify or discontinue portions or our entire Platform with or without notice and without liability to you or any third party.</string>
    <string name="partytext">The Platform contains links to third party sites and is integrated with various third party services, applications and sites that may make available to you their content and products. We don’t control these third parties and aren’t responsible for those sites or services or their content or products. These third parties may have their own terms and policies and your use of them will be governed by those terms and policies.</string>
    <string name="relesetext">As we do not supervise or control (a) the events organised by members, (b) interactions among or (c) between members of Impromptu events (and other persons or companies) and because we are not involved in any way with (a) physical transportation to or from Impromptu events or (b) with the actions of any individuals at Impromptu events and because we do not control Amazon.com, PayPal, credit card companies or other payment processing companies and because we cannot guarantee the true identity, age, nationality of Platform users and because we have very limited control, if any, over the quality, safety, morality, legality, truthfulness or accuracy of various aspects of the Platform, you agree that you bear all risk and you agree to release us (and our officers, directors, shareholders, agents, employees, affiliates, subsidiaries, and third party partners) and Organisers and Creators or Hosts and their designees from claims, demands, and damages (actual and consequential) of every kind and nature, known and unknown, suspected and unsuspected, disclosed and undisclosed, now and in the future, arising out of or in any way connected with your use of the Platform, your Third Party Transactions, our resolution of any disputes among users, and/or your transportation to or from, attendance at, or the actions of you or other persons at an Impromptu event. You further waive any and all rights and benefits otherwise conferred by any statutory or non-statutory law of any jurisdiction that would purport to limit the scope of a release or waiver.</string>
    <string name="indementiontext">You agree to indemnify, defend and hold all Impromptu Parties harmless from any Claims, made by any third party due to or arising out of (a) your violations of this Agreement, (b) your use, misuse, or abuse of our Platform, (c) your Content, (d) your violation of any law, statute, ordinance or regulation or the rights of a third party, or (e) your participation or conduct in an Impromptu event that violates this Agreement. You agree to promptly notify us of any third party Claims, cooperate with all Impromptu Parties in defending such Claims and pay all fees, costs and expenses associated with defending such Claims (including, but not limited to, attorneys’ fees). You agree not to settle any Claim without our prior written consent.</string>
    <string name="diclaimertext">Our Platform is provided to you “as is” and on an “as available” basis. We disclaim all warranties and conditions of any kind, including but not limited to statutory warranties and the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. We also disclaim any warranties regarding (a) the reliability, timeliness, accuracy and performance of our Platform, (b) any information, advice, services, or goods obtained through or advertised on our Platform or by us, (c) any information or advice received through any links to other websites or resources provided through our Platform, (d) the results that may be obtained from the Platform,  (e) the correction of any errors in the Platform, (f) any material or data obtained through the use of our Platform and (g) dealings with or as the result of the presence of marketing partners or other third parties on or located through our Platform.</string>
    <string name="limitationtext">You agree that in no event shall any Impromptu Parties be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages. This is including, but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, data or other intangible losses (even if any Impromptu Parties have been advised of the possibility of such damages) arising out of or in connection with (a) our Platform or this Agreement or the inability to use our Platform (however arising, including our negligence), (b) statements, conduct of, transactions with any member or third party on the Platform, (c) your use of our Platform or transportation to or from Impromptu events, attendance at Impromptu events, participation in or exclusion from Impromptu events and the actions of you or others at Impromptu events, or (d) any other matter relating to the Platform. Our liability to you or any third parties in any circumstance is limited to the greater of £100 or the amount of fees, if any, you paid to us in the 12 months prior to the action that may give rise to liability. The limitations set forth above in this Section 8 will not limit or exclude liability for our gross negligence, fraud or intentional, malicious or reckless misconduct.</string>
    <string name="resolutiontext">Prior to making any claim, you and Impromptu agree to try to resolve any disputes through ‘good faith’ discussions. The “claim” in this instance refers to any dispute, claim or controversy arising from or relating to your use of our Platform or this Agreement. This includes your participation in Impromptu events. You or Impromptu may initiate this process by sending written notice according to Section 11.1 detailing the dispute and your proposal for resolution.</string>
    <string name="ipimpromytutext">Impromptu logos, trademarks and service marks/names are the IP of Impromptu Social. Our Platform (including our material on the Platform) form part of our (or our licensors) IP. You agree not to use our IP without our prior written consent.</string>
    <string name="otherstext">Impromptu respects the IP of others and we expect our members to do the same. We may, in specific circumstances and at our discretion, remove or disable access to material that infringes on the IP rights of others. We may also restrict or terminate the accounts of users that we believe to be repeat offenders.</string>
    <string name="noticetext">Except as otherwise stated in this Agreement or as expressly required by law, any notice to us shall be given by certified postal mail to Impromptu Social Limited., 257 Falcon House, Burlington Road, London KT3 4NE. Any notice to you shall be given to the most current email address used on your account.</string>
    <string name="agencytext">No agency, partnership, joint venture, employee-employer or partner relationship between you and Impromptu is intended or created by this Agreement. A member of the Impromptu Platform is not Impromptu’s representative or agent, and may not enter into an agreement on Impromptu’s behalf.</string>
    <string name="lawtext">This Agreement and the relationship between you and Impromptu shall be governed by the laws of the Supreme Court of the United Kingdom</string>
    <string name="assignmettext">This Agreement is not assignable, transferable or sub-licensable by you except with Impromptu’s prior written consent. It may be assigned or transferred by us to any affiliate or subsidiary, or in connection with a merger, acquisition, corporate reorganisation or sale (of all or substantially all of Impromptu’s assets or a similar transaction).</string>
    <string name="waivertext">A party’s failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of this Agreement shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision and does not waive any right to act with respect to subsequent or similar breaches.</string>
    <string name="severencetext">If any provision of this Agreement is found to be invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, you and Impromptu nevertheless agree that the court should endeavour to give effect to the parties’ intentions as reflected in the provision and that the other provisions of this Agreement will remain in full force and effect.</string>
    <string name="terminationtext">If we terminate your account or access to our Platform, this Agreement terminates with respect to the member account that has been terminated. However, certain provisions of this Agreement that by their nature survive termination shall survive termination, including those terms listed below in Section 11.9 (Survival).</string>
    <string name="survivaltext">Sections 3 (Fees, Payments, and Promotions), 4.1 (Privacy), 4.3 (Content License from You), 6 (Release), 7 (Indemnification), 8 (Warranty Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability), 9 (Dispute Resolution), 11 (Miscellaneous) and 11.8 (Termination) of this Agreement, and any other provisions necessary to give effect to these provisions shall survive any termination or expiration of this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="viloationtext">Please report any violations of this Agreement by a member or third party by sending an email to support@impromptu.com.</string>
    <string name="viloationtext2">Thank you!  "\n""\n"Please accept our gratitude for reading our Terms of Service."\n""\n"</string>
    <string name="privancytext1">By using Impromptu’s services, you consent to the collection and use of your data as described in this Privacy Policy. Please carefully read the following to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, disclose, protect and otherwise handle information about you.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx2"><u>Information You Provide To Us</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx3">The types of information we may collect include: "\n""\n"• Basic user information, such as your name, gender, birth date, email address, profile images and social photographs."\n""\n"• Messages and interactive chat information, such as messages to other Impromptu users, comments on event message boards and information you provide in connection with events you post to the Platform. "\n""\n"• Other background,contact and demographic information,such as your occupation,social event history,interests and self-descriptions you choose to provide."\n"• Information about you from other Impromptu users,such as friend invites,reviews of events you host,feedback sent and received by you and other interconnections and interactions between you and other Impromptu users.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx4"><u>Information We Collect Automatically</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx5">When you access,or use our Services,we may also automatically collect information about you.This may include:"\n""\n"• Location Information: We may collect information about your location when you access our mobile application,or otherwise consent to the collection of this information."\n""\n"• Device Information: We collect device-specific information when you access our Services,including your hardware model,operating system and version,unique device identifiers,mobile network information and information about the device’s interaction with our Services."\n""\n"• Log Information: We collect log information about how you access or use our Services,including your access times,operating system type,language,Internet Service Provider and Internet Protocol (“IP”) address."\n""\n"• Information Collected by Cookies and other Trackers: We or our third party services we use to improve your experience may automatically collect information using cookies and other tracking technologies to,among other things count visits,understand usage of the service and campaign effectiveness and tell,for example,if an email has been opened and acted upon.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx6"><u>Information We Collect from Other Sources</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx7">We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services.For example,if you create or log into your Impromptu account through a third-party social networking site,we will have access to certain information from that site,such as your name,profile picture and other account information in accordance with the authorisation procedures determined by said third-party site.But other than your first name,surname,gender,and profile photo,no other information from third-party social networking sites is shared with other users.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx8"><u>How Do We Use this Information?</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx9">We use information about you for purposes described in this Privacy Policy or otherwise disclosed to you on or in connection with our Services.For example, we may use information about you to:"\n""\n"• Operate and improve our Services."\n""\n"• Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support/administrative messages."\n""\n"• Respond to your comments,questions,requests and provide customer service."\n""\n"• Communicate with you about products,services,offers,promotions,rewards,events and provide other news/information about Impromptu and other third parties. "\n""\n"• Monitor and analyze trends,usage and activities in connection with our Services."\n""\n"• Tailor the Services,which may include providing content or features that match user profiles or interests.We retain the personal data you provide until your account is deleted.Account deactivation does not delete your personal data.In some cases we may retain certain information in anonymised or aggregated form.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx10"><u>Overseas Transfer of Your Personal Information</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx11">We may store and process personal information in the United Kingdom,United States and other countries,where under local laws you may have fewer legal rights.Regardless of where we store your information,we will treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Impromptu Social Limited complies with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Framework as set forth by the European Union Parliament regarding the collection,use,and retention of personal information of all individuals within the European Union and the export of personal data outside the EU.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx12"><u>Sharing of Information</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx13">We will not share information about you with outside parties except as described below or elsewhere in this Privacy Policy:"\n""\n"• With your consent"\n""\n"• With third party vendors,consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out their work on our behalf.This includes Stripe,the provider of our secure payment processing service."\n""\n"• With others who access or use our Services in accordance with the privacy settings you establish"\n""\n"• With search engines in order to index the content you provide as part of a group or public profile"\n""\n"• With partners who run contests,special offers or other events or activities in connection with our Services."\n""\n"• In connection with,or during negotiations of,any merger,sale of company assets,financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company."\n""\n"• If we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law,regulation,legal process or governmental request,including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements."\n""\n"• To enforce our agreements,policies and Terms and Conditions (to protect the security or integrity of our Services,or to protect Impromptu,our users or the public from harm or illegal activities.We may also share aggregated or de-identified information,which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.Impromptu is responsible and liable if third-party agents that it uses to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the GDPR,unless Impromptu proves that it is not responsible for the event that allowed the damage to occur.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx14"><u>Social Media Tools</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx15">Impromptu may offer social sharing features or other integrated tools which let you share actions you take on our platform with other media (and vice versa). The use of such features enables the sharing of certain information with your friends or the public,depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides the social sharing feature.For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features,please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these social sharing features.Impromptu may also allow you to access Google Maps.Please note that when you use Google Maps,you are subject to Google’s privacy policy ,as amended by Google sporadically.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx16"><u>Third Party Links</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx17">We may occasionally include or offer third party products or services as part of our Services.This will be at our discretion.These third parties may have separate and independent privacy policies.We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the activities of these third parties and how they collect,use or share information about you.Nonetheless,we seek to protect the integrity of our services and welcome any feedback about these third parties.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx18"><u>Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx19">We may allow third parties to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services in relation to the use of our Services.These entities may use cookies,web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites,including your IP address and information about your web browser and operating system,pages viewed,time spent on pages,links clicked and conversion information.This information may be used by Impromptu and others to,among other things,analyze and track data,determine the popularity of certain content,deliver content tailored to your interests on our Services and better understand your online activity.Please note that we may share aggregated,non-personal information,or personal information in a hashed,non-human readable form, with these third parties.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx20"><u>How Do We Protect Visitor Information?</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx21">We take security of your data seriously and take reasonable measures to protect information about you from loss,theft,misuse,unauthorised access,disclosure,alteration and destruction.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx22">Your Information Choices</string>
    <string name="privancytetx23"><u>Privacy Settings</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx24">We will only collect and process personal data about you where we have a lawful basis.Lawful bases include,but are not limited to,situations where:"\n""\n"• you having given consent."\n""\n"• processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you."\n""\n"• processing is necessary for the legitimate interests pursued by Impromptu,as deemed lawful under the GDPR Regulation."\n""\n"• processing is necessary for the compliance of a legal obligation. https://www.eugdpr.org/ Learn more here."\n"You have many choices about your data: "\n""\n"• You can update and correct most of your personal data through your account.If this is not possible,you can ask us to update your data,particularly in cases of inaccuracy,by contacting Customer Support."\n""\n"• You can opt-out of email marketing from the emails themselves."\n""\n"• You can ask us to restrict or limit the processing of your data."\n""\n"• You may also revoke your consent to processing and ask us to delete your data.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx25"><u>Account Information</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx26">You may update or correct information about you at any time by logging into your account and editing your profile.You may deactivate or delete your account and personal data entirely by logging into your account and clicking on the relevant link in Settings.Even after you deactivate or delete your account,we may retain certain information for legitimate business purposes or to protect member safety.If your account is deactivated,Impromptu will provide access to the data associated with the deactivated account upon receipt of the required legal documentation.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx27"><u>Location Information via Mobile</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx28">You have the ability to turn location-based services on and off by adjusting the settings of your mobile device and by following the standard uninstall process and removing Impromptu’s application from your device.Doing so,however,may mean that you cannot use all or a portion of our Services.</string>
    <string name="privancytetx29"><u>Contact Us</u></string>
    <string name="privancytetx30">If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy,please contact us via post at 257 Burlington Road,KT3 4NE,United Kingdom."\n""\n"In addition,EU members can direct privacy-related inquiries or complaints to support@impromptusocial.com.Any dispute,claim or controversy arising out of or relating to this Policy or previous Privacy Policy statements shall be resolved through negotiation,mediation and arbitration,as provided under our Terms of Service Agreement."\n""\n"This Privacy Policy is governed by the terms of Impromptu’s Terms and Conditions.""\n</string>
    <string name="nointernettext">Something seems to have gone wrong. "\n"Please try again...</string>


</resources>
